你想他们有昨天的报纸吗?
Do you think they have yesterday's Daily News?
我只是想看我的星座准不准
I just wanna check my horoscope,see if it was right.
天啊,菲比,别看 你背后有个将会令我们
Oh,my God! Don't Iook now. Behind you there's a guy...
伤心欲绝的帅哥
...who can break our hearts and plunge us into depression.
到妈妈这来呀
Come to mama.
他来了,酷一点…
He's coming. Be cool. Be cool. Be cool.
-帽子不错 -谢谢
-Nice hat. -Thanks.
-我们应该有所行动,吹口哨 -我不吹
-We should do something. Whistle. -I' m not whistling.
来吧,吹!
Come on,do it!
吹.吹.吹
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
我不敢相信你居然这么干了
I can't believe you did that.
六人行 第1季 第11集 宾太太
The One With Mrs. Bing
-这都是我的错 -不,是我的错
-It's all my fault. -No,it's mine.
我为什么要“喔-呵”的叫呢?
Why did I whoo-hoo?
难道我期望,他回过头来然后说…
Was I hoping he'd turn around and say...
…“我喜欢那声音,我现在就要你”?
... " I Iove that sound. I must have you now"?
我只希望我们能帮上一点忙
I wish there was something we could do.
你好,昏迷的帅哥
Hello,coma guy.
起来,你这少女侦察机! 起来!起来!起来!
Get up,you Girl Scout! Up,up,up!
菲比,你在干什么?
What are you doing?
或许没人试过这一招
Maybe nobody's tried this.
希望至少能知道他的名字
I wish we at Ieast knew his name.
我讨厌他们叫他“某约翰”(无名氏)
I hate that they're calling him John Doe.
这真让人伤心.感觉他像一只小鹿 一只小雌鹿
It's so sad. It's Iike he's a deer,a female deer.
喔,我就此打住
Oh,I was gonna stop.
瞧他这张脸
Look at that face.
即使他在昏迷中仍一副聪明样
Even sleeping he Iooks smart.
你有看见他手关节上的凹凸吗? 那代表他有艺术气息
Yeah,but the dents in his knuckles mean he's artistic.
他是个兼职教雕塑的律师
Okay. He's a Iawyer who teaches sculpting on the side.
而且他会跳舞
And he can dance.
他是那种静静听你讲话的人
And he's the kind of guy who,when you're talking,he's listening...
而不是说“我了解”
... not saying," I understand "...
却猜想着你裸体的样子
... but really wondering what you Iook Iike naked.
我希望男生都像他这样
I wish all guys could be Iike him.
我知道
I know.
你们甚至不认识这小伙
You don't even know this guy.
纽约难道没有适合你们的清醒男生?
Are there no conscious men in the city for you two?
他身旁没人照顾
He doesn't have anyone.
我们觉得应该负起责任
We feel kind of responsible.
我不敢相信你会“喔-呵”
I can't believe you said "whoo-hoo. "
连我都不说“喔-呵”
I don't even say "whoo-hoo. "
哦,她出现了
Oh,she's coming up.
稍后,我们将和永远引人人胜的 诺拉.泰勒.宾进行访谈
When we return,we 'll talk with the always interesting Nora Tyler Bing.
你得叫你的孩子上床睡觉了
Put the kids to bed for this one.
我们别看这个 HBO电影台正在播《老板度假去》
Don't watch this. Weekend at Bernie 's is on Showtime and HBO.
不行,这怎么可以
No way.
-她是你妈妈! -没错. 但是《老板度假去》里面
-She's your mom. -Exactly. Weekend at Bernie 's.
死人的腹股沟被打了二,三十次
Dead guy getting hit in the groin 20,30 times.
钱德,我得告诉你 我爱你妈的书
I gotta tell you,I Iove your mom's books.
飞机上没她的书陪伴,我会度日如年 她的书简直是酷毙了
I can't get on a plane without one. This is so cool.
你无法想象当你11岁的时候
You wouldn't think so if you were 1 1...
你的朋友们争相传阅 “情妇婊子”79页时的感觉
...and your friends were passing around page 79 of Mistress Bitch.
我记得第79页
I remember page 79.
歌剧之后 和那个有可爱臀部的小姑娘的故事
The thing after the opera with the girl with the trick hip?
拜托,我爱你妈.她是第一流的
I Iove your mom. I think she's a blast.
这是因为她不是你妈妈
That's because she's not your mom.
拜托
Oh,please. She's the
亲爱的
Hi,sweetie.
那个“波纹贝壳状通心粉(意大利菜)” 什么时候从罗马回来的?
When did " Rigatoni " get back from Rome?
-昨晚 -真的?
-Last night. -Really?
难道,他的飞机没在空中炸成火球?
So,his plane didn't explode in a big ball of fire?
只是我做过的一个梦
Just a dream I had.
但,呼!
But,phew!
她出现了
Hey,she's on.
诺拉宾
Nora Bing.
等会儿再谈你的书吧 听说你在伦敦被逮捕?
Back to the book. What is this about you being arrested in London?
你妈被逮捕?
Your mom was arrested?
安静,我正感到无比的骄傲
I'm busy beaming with pride.
说来有点难为情…
This is kind of embarrassing...
…在我不经意和一个男人亲热后
...but occasionally,after I've been intimate with a man...
她怎会说难为情?
Why would she say that's embarrassing?
…我非常想吃宫保鸡丁
...I just get this craving for kung pao chicken.
透露太多了!
That's too much information.
不必说,他当然有一个大家伙
Needless to say,he got a huge tip.
哦,上帝,我爱她!
Oh,God,I Iove her!
我想我快要中风了
I think I' m having a stroke.
现在你正为新书做宣传,情况如何?
So how is your book tour going?
还不错,明天我将前往纽约 其实我不喜欢纽约
Oh,fine. I'm leaving for New York tomorrow,which I hate.
但是我的儿子住那儿,我爱他
But I get to see my son,who I love.
这就是我了解这个的方式. 而大多数母亲只会透过电话这么说
This is the way that I find out. Most moms use the phone.
别误会,只是我看不出你已为人母
Don 't take this wrong,I just don 't see you as a mom.
-我绝对没有恶意 -不,我是个很前卫的母亲
-I don 't mean that bad. -Oh,no. I'm a fabulous mom.
我儿子的第一个保险套,是我买给他的
I bought my son his first condoms.
然后他就欲火焚身
And then he burst into flames.
国会正讨论新削减预算赤字法案
Let's see. Congress is debating a new deficit-reduction bill.
市长想再度提高地铁票价 今天最高气温是45度
The mayor wants to raise subway fares. The high today was 45.
还有各球队正在比赛
And teams played sports.
格伦如何?
What about GIen?
可以叫他格伦
He could be a GIen.
不,还不够特别
Not special enough.
阿伽门农(荷马史诗英雄)怎么样?
How about Agamemnon?
太特别了
Way too special.
我饿死了,我想吃什么呢?
I'm famished. What do I want?
拜托,别又是宫保鸡丁
PIease,God,don't Iet it be kung pao chicken.
你看了那节目,感觉如何?
You watched the show. What did you think?
我觉得你应该更放开一些…
I think you need to come out of your shell.
为何选在这里?
What is this dive?
只有你才会选这种地方
Only you could've picked this place.
闭嘴,这样满不错的 来,抱一个
Come on. Shut up. It's fun. Give me a hug.
我听说了离婚的事情了.女同性恋?
I heard about the divorce. Lesbian,huh?
你知道他们总是说:“要小心你内心希望的.”
Well,you know what they say: Be careful what you wish for.
-我想我们可以喝点龙舌酒了 -我知道我可以
-I think we' re ready for some tequila. -I know I am.
-谁要来一杯 -我要
-Who's doing shots? -Hit me.
你呢,罗斯?
There you go. Ross?
我不喝酒
I' m not really a shot-drinking kind of guy.
抱歉,我们迟到了
Hi. Sorry we' re Iate.
我们有点忘了时间
We kind of just,you know,Iost track of time.
不过男人是可以改变的
But a man can change.
有人要我评价任何事物吗?
Anyone want me to appraise anything?
我要去方便一下
Well,I' m gonna go to tinker-town.
宾太太,我拜读过你所有的大作
Mrs. Bing,I've read everything you've written.
我读了《兴奋午夜》后,就一心想成为作家
When I read Euphoria at Midnight,I wanted to become a writer.
别这么说,我能办到的大家都能办到
Oh,please. If I can do it,anybody can.
你只需先描述半打欧洲城市
Start with half a dozen European cities...
以30个委婉语形容男性生殖器
...throw in 30 euphemisms for male genitalia...
这样就能写成一本书了
...and you've got yourself a book.
女士们先生们,这就是我母亲
My mother,ladies and gentlemen.
226房有留言吗?
Yeah,any messages for room 226?
-你还好吧,猛男? -我还好
-You okay,slugger? -Oh,yeah. I' m fine.
你今晚怎么了?
What is with you tonight?
没什么……
Nothing. Nothing,nothing.
谢谢
Okay,thank you.
是因为那个意大利舔手男?
It's the Italian hand-licker,isn't it?
不,是因为被他舔的人
No. It's the one he's Iicking.
她应该和你在一起
She's supposed to be with you.
你真行
You' re good.
罗斯,我卖出上亿本的书 知道为什么吗?
I have sold 1 00 million copies of my books,and you know why?
因为封面上的辣妹露两点?
The girl on the cover with her nipples showing?
不,因为我知道该如何描写让女人陷入爱河的男人
No,because I know how to write men that women fall in Iove with.
相信我,保罗没有卖点
I cannot sell a Paolo.
没人有兴趣翻325页看保罗的
People will not turn 325 pages for a Paolo.
他不过是个二等货
Come on. The guy's a secondary character.
不过是最后要被你打败的
He's just a complication you eventually kill off.
什么时候?
When?
他不是主角
He's not a hero.
知道我们的最佳男主角是谁?
You know who our hero is?
露两点的猛男?
The guy on the cover with his nipples showing?
是你啊
No,it's you.
-不要这么说 -不,我是说真的
-PIease. -No,really.
你既聪明又性感
Come on. You' re smart. You' re sexy.
-真的 -是呀
-Right. -Yes,you are.
事实是,你不认为自己比以前更性感了
The fact that you don't think you are makes you sexier.
你会走出阴霾的,相信我
Come on,kiddo. You' re gonna be fine,believe me.
我到街上尿就好了
I'II just pee in the street.
钱德在吗
Is Chandler here?
等等.过来
Wait. Come here.
关于昨天晚上
Okay,about Iast night...
你知道的
...you know...
钱德,你没有告诉他吧
... Chandler,you didn't tell....
因为我想不需告诉他 只是个吻,没什么大不了的
We don't need to tell Chandler. It was just a kiss. No big deal,right?
对,没什么大不了的
Right. No big deal.
在奇异世界中才叫没什么
In bizarro world.
你违反规定
You broke the code.
-什么规定? -不能亲朋友母亲的规定
-What code? -You don't kiss your friend's mom.
姐妹还可以 火辣的姑妈,或许也行
Sisters are okay. Maybe a hot-looking aunt.
母亲不行,绝对不行
But not a mom. Never a mom.
你们在外面干什么?
What are you guys doing out here?
乔伊和我说过要早起去打壁球
Joey and I had discussed getting in an early morning racquetball game.
显然有人睡过头了
But apparently somebody overslept.
对,你没带球拍?
Well,you don't have your racquet.
不,我的拍子拿去修了
No. No,I don't because it's being restrung.
有人应该帮我准备一支拍子
Somebody was supposed to bring me one.
是吗?你没告诉我握把的尺寸
Well,you didn't call and leave your grip size.
你们俩真会浪费时间
You guys are spending way too much time together.
好吧,我是人渣,我是人渣
I' m scum. I' m scum.
-罗斯,你怎能让这种事发生? -我也不知道
-How could you Iet this happen? -I don't know.
她不像是一般的妈妈
It's not Iike she's a regular mom.
她很性感
She's sexy. She's....
你认为我妈不性感?
You don't think my mom's sexy?
不一样的性感
Well,not in the same way.
我妈当年也是美得不得了
I'll have you know,GIoria T ribbiani was a handsome woman in her day.
你认为生7个小孩是件容易的事?
You think it's easy giving birth to seven children?
我们愈谈愈离谱了
Okay,I think we're getting into a weird area here.
你们在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
不是打壁球
Not playing racquetball.
-他忘了告诉我握把尺寸 -他没带护目镜
-He forgot to Ieave his grip size. -He didn't get the goggles.
你们俩似乎有点事
Sounds Iike you two have issues.
再见,宝贝
Goodbye,baby.
他们是故意做给我看的吗?
Do they wait for me to do this?
-你到底要不要告诉他? -为何要告诉他?
-Are you gonna tell him? -Why would I tell him?
如果你不说，他妈或许会
If you don't,his mother might.
你们在这儿干什么?
What are you guys doing here?
他没穿护裆
He's not even wearing a jock strap.
我刚问了什么?
What did I ask?
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
没事,我只是顺路… 我被那个,你知道的,就是那个
Nothing. I just thought I'd stop by,you know,after...
那个,我,你知道的
...that I,you know.
你来这儿干什么?
So,what are you doing here?
我不是专程来此
I' m not really here.
只是顺路拿这些过来
I just thought I'd drop these off on the way. My way.
你常自己来?
Do you come here a Iot...
一个人来?
...without me?
不，不，不
No,no,no.
你认为他早上好点没?
Do you think he's doing any better than he was this morning?
我怎会知道?我又没来
How would I know? I wasn't here.
真的?也没替他换睡衣?
Really? Not even to change his pajamas?
我的天
Oh,my God.
你是我朋友,我得告诉你
You're my friend. I had to tell you.
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe it.
保罗亲了我妈?
Paolo kissed my mom?
对,我不知道你是否注意到 他喝了很多酒
I don't know if you noticed,but he drank a Iot.
他酒醉的模样你也见识过
I mean,you know how he gets
我办不到…是我
I can't do this. I did it.
抱歉,是我亲了你妈
It was me. I' m sorry. I kissed your mom.
什么?
What?
瑞秋和保罗的事令我很沮丧 我想我是喝太多龙舌酒,而诺拉
I was upset about Rachel and I had too much tequila,and Nora...
妈妈太太,你的宾
... Mrs. Mom,your Bing,was...
你的妈妈对我很体贴 但没发生什么事
... being nice. But nothing happened.
什么都没有,可以问乔伊
Nothing. Ask Joey.
-乔伊刚好走进来 -你知道这件事?
-Joey came in -You knew about this?
知识是很狡猾的
You know,knowledge is a tricky thing.
你为何没告诉我?
Why didn't you tell me?
他们被我逮到算你幸运 不然后果可不堪设想
You're Iucky I caught them,or else who knows what would've happened?
谢了,老兄,帮大忙了
Thanks,man. Big help.
你到底在想什么?
What the hell were you thinking?
我没有…我不知道
I wasn't. I don't know. I
我和我妈之间的事 朋友中属你最清楚了
No one knows the crap I go through with my mom more than you.
-我知道 -我无法相信你会做这种事
-I know. -I can't believe you did this.
-我也无法相信 -我也对你很生气
-Me neither. -I' m mad at you too.
-为什么生我的气? -让我用力关门吧
-Why are you mad at me? -Let me slam the door.
钱德,我又没亲她,违反规定就是这种下场
I didn't kiss her. See what happens when you break the code?
“丢脸的女人”瑞秋凯伦格林
"A Woman Undone,by Rachel Karen Greene. "
对,我想尝试一下,我仍在写第一章
I thought I'd give it a shot. I'm on the first chapter.
你认为他“粗棉布监牢”中的“爱棒” 能获得解放吗?
Do you think his "Iove stick" can be "Iiberated from its denim prison"?
我想可以吧
Yeah,I'd say so.
另外，“engorged（充盈的）”这个单词没有“J”
And there's no "J " in "engorged. "
-你今晚要去医院吗? -不,你呢?
-You going to the hospital tonight? -No. You?
不,你呢?
No. You?
你刚问过了
You just asked me.
好吧,或许这是个圈套
Maybe it was a trick question.
瑞秋,我们现在能开始了吗?
Rachel,can we do this now?
我好兴奋
I am so hot.
这是我爸妈在婚礼时照的
Here's my mom and dad on their wedding day.
你告诉我,她不是旷世美人
Now,you tell me she's not a knockout.
-没想到我们会谈论这个 -就试着想像她没挺着大肚子
-I can't believe this conversation. -Just try to picture her not pregnant.
中央公园很荣幸为各位介绍 菲比布菲小姐
Central Perk is proud to present Miss Phoebe Buffay.
谢谢
Thanks.
这首歌是有关一个我刚认识的男生
I'd Iike to start with a song about a man I recently met...
他已成为我生命中重要的男人
...who's come to be very important to me.
你无须醒来当我的男人
You don 't have to be awake To be my man
只要你还有脑电波 我就会在一旁握着你的手
Long as you have brain waves I'll be there to hold your hand
虽然我们相遇不久
Though we just met the other day
我想说…
There 's something I have got to say
谢谢各位,我得休息一下
Thank you very much. I' m gonna take a short break.
我们感谢菲比小姐
That was Phoebe Buffay,everybody.
-她在搞什么? -菲比刚…
-What the hell was that? -Phoebe just started
我是和乔伊讲话,行了，亲妈妈的人
I was talking to Joey. AII right,there,mother-kisser?
亲妈妈的人
" Mother-kisser. "
我闭嘴
I'II shut up.
我知道你仍在生我的气
I know you' re still mad at me...
我只想说那一夜有两个人
... but there were two people there that night.
-两双嘴唇 -是哦,我希望她亲口告诉我
-There were two sets of Iips. -I expect this from her.
她一直都是个弗洛伊德噩梦
She's always been a Freudian nightmare.
你为何不找她谈谈?
Then why don't you say something?
因为太复杂了,这太复杂了
Because it's complicated. It's complex.
你亲了我妈
You kissed my mom.
我们正在排练希腊剧
We' re rehearsing a Greek play.
真幽默,排练完没?
That's funny. Are we done now?
还没,你为何不找她说出你的感受?
You mean you' re not gonna tell her how you feel?
别因为你亲过她
Just because you played tonsil tennis with my mom...
就自以为了解她 相信我,不能找她谈
...doesn't mean you know her. You can't talk to her.
是你“不能”还是“你”不能?
Okay. "You can't"? Or you can't?
我的手指
Okay,that's my finger.
我的膝盖
Okay,that's my knee.
还在排练
Still doing the play.
你对他怎么了?
What did you do with him?
-你醒了 -你瞧你
-You're awake. -Look at you.
感觉如何?
How do you feel?
头有点晕,基本上还行
A Iittle woozy,but basically okay.
你的气色好极了
Gosh,you Iook good.
我感觉好极了
I feel good.
你们是谁?
Who are you?
-对不起 -我叫菲比
-Sorry. -I'm Phoebe.
我叫莫妮卡 我一直在照顾你
I' m Monica. I've been caring for you.
我们一直在照顾你
We both have.
-蚀刻艺术是你们送的? -其实只有我一个
-The Etch A Sketch is from you? -Actually,me.
-我替你做脚底按摩 -知道是谁帮你刮胡子的吗?是我
-I got you the foot massager. -I shaved you.
-我念书给你听 -我唱歌给你听
-I read to you. -I sang.
谢了
Well,thanks.
-我的荣幸 -没关系
-Oh,my pleasure. -You' re welcome.
我想那就再见了
So I guess I'II see you around.
什么?就这样?
What? That's it?
再见?
"See you around "?
-不然要我说什么? -我不知道
-What do you want me to say? -I don't know.
或许
Maybe...
该说“你们真好”
... "That was nice. "
“我太感动了”
" It meant something to me. "
“我会打电话给你们的”
" I'II call you. "
-好吧,我会打的 -一点诚意都没有
-Okay. I'II call you. -I don't think you mean that.
男生都这样
This is so typical.
我们付出,付出
You know,we give and we give...
不断的付出
...and we give.
却得不到任何回报
And we just get nothing back.
有一天他醒来却只说再见
And then one day,you wake up,and it's,"See you around. "
走吧菲比
Let's go,Phoebe.
知道吗?我们以为你与众不同
You know what? We thought you were different.
我想这只是昏迷的缘故
But I guess it was just the coma.
楼下的车已发动 我只想拿几本我的书给你朋友
The car's waiting. I just wanted to drop off my book for your friends.
有我的亲笔签名.来一个吻别
Autographed. And give you a goodbye kiss.
这是一个吻 这是告别…
Here's the kiss,here's the goodbye....
-需要我在里斯本帮你买什么吗? -不需要,知道你去哪就够了
-Anything you want from Lisbon? -Just knowing you' re there is enough.
好吧,要乖哦,我爱你
AII right. Well,be good. I Iove you.
你亲了我最好的罗斯
You kissed my best Ross.
好像说错了,反正差不多
Or something to that effect.
好吧,我做了蠢事
Look,it was stupid.
-愚蠢至极 -愚蠢至极
-Really stupid. -Really stupid.
我也不知道是怎么发生的
I don't even know how it happened.
抱歉,孩子,我保证不会再发生这种事
I' m sorry,honey. I promise it will never happen again.
真的愚蠢至极
Really,really stupid.
真的,真的愚蠢至极
-你感觉好点吗? -是的
-Are we okay now? -Yeah.
不
No.
男人与门之间禁忌的爱
The forbidden Iove of a man and his door.
他说了,不只是亲吻的事 一切都说出来了
He told her off. And not just about the kiss.
你在开玩笑?
You're kidding?
他说你何时才能像个妈妈样子?
He said,"When are you gonna start being a mom? "
等等,她回答说
Then she said:
你何时才能长大了解 我是个性感女郎?
"The question is,when are you gonna realize I have a bomb? "
等等,你确定她不是说
Are you sure she didn't say:
你何时才能长大了解 我是你妈?
"When are you gonna grow up and realize I am your mom? "
-这样比较合理 -你也这样认为?
-That makes more sense. -You think?
现在情况怎么样?
What's going on now?
我不知道.我一直在这儿说给你听
I don't know. I've been standing here spelling it out for you.
我什么都听不到,等等…
I don't hear anything. Wait.
你看见什么?
What do you see?
很难说,他们好小而且上下颠倒
It's hard to tell. They're tiny and upside down.
等等，等等
Wait,wait,wait.
他们走过来,他们走过去
They're walking away. They're walking away.
不,不是.他们走过来了,快逃
No,they' re not. They' re coming right at us. Run!
-你还好吧,孩子? -还好
-Are you okay,kiddo? -Yeah,I' m okay.
希望都好
AII right. You be good.
小心开车
Drive safe.
-你好,宾太太 -你好,盖勒先生
-Mrs. Bing. -Mr. Geller.
你当真?
You mean that?
对,有何不可?
Yeah,why not?
我告诉她了
So I told her.
-情况怎么样? -简直是可笑到了极点
-How did it go? -Awful. Awful.
没有比这更糟糕的啦
Couldn't have gone worse.
-感觉怎样 -不错
-Well,how do you feel? -Pretty good.
我告诉她了
I told her.
瞧,看到没有?
Well,see?
或许我亲你妈不是个馊主意…
So maybe it wasn't such a bad idea,me kissing your mom,huh?
我们不必继续往下说了吧
But we don't have to go down that road.
这只是第一章
This is just the first chapter...
我要大家坦白的意见
...and I want your absolute honest opinion. Okay?
在第二页中 他的手没伸向她那尖挺的胸部
And on page two,he's not reaching for her " heaving beasts. "
她可以有尖挺的胸部
She could have heaving beasts.
没错,但现在这个状态她没有
Right,but in this case she doesn't.
什么是“niffle”（应为nipple乳头）?
What's a " niffle"?
通常在坚挺的胸部可以找到
You can usually find them on the heaving beasts.
好吧…算我不会打字
Okay,so I' m not a great typist.
看这里：“他那巨大,颤动的‘笔’（应为penis阴茎）”
Did you get to the part about his "huge,throbbing pens"?
他用那支笔时你不会想在场的
You don't wanna be around when he starts writing with those.
够了,还我…
That's it. Give them back.
等等,我才刚刚看到她的“公共头发（应为pubic hair阴毛）”
Wait,I just got to the part about her "public hair. "